Guide to the Aaron Cometbus Punk and Underground Press Collection, ca. 1977-2013.
Cometbus, Aaron Punk and Underground Press Collection
- Series VI. Ephemera, 1979-2018
  - Assorted Ephemera, 1982-2018
    - Punk Buttons, Undated; MU-1691-1700, 1878-1879 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Includes buttons from Dead Kennedys, White Flag, Psychedelic Furs, Trial, Vicious Circle, KALX, Flipside Video, The Witnesses, The Contractions, and Aaardvark's Odd Ark.
    - Punk Greeting Cards, 1982-1994 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Radio, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Includes KSAN 95FM poster and Free Radio Ashville sticker and flyer
      Berkeley, California; Asheville, North Carolina
    - Radio, Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Includes KSAN 95FM poster and Free Radio Asheville flyer.
    - Radio - KALX Program Guide, 1984-1985; Griffin, Paul (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Radio - Ten Watts, 1981-02-1981-08; Herd, Angela; Van Buskirk, Lisa (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Subterranean Calendars, 1999-12-2003-02 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Community calendar of upcoming cultural events and historical dates, started by Aaron Cometbus and edited by a revolving cast, named after community hub, Subterranean Books
    - Record and Tape Trade/Want Lists, 1984-1989; Cometbus, Aaron; Banks, Ken; Yee, Eric (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Punk Trading Cards, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      Contains cards from Wisconsin(1995) and the Superchunk (Chunk)/Seaweed/Geek tour(1990)
    - Exhibit of artwork by Joanne Segal Brandford, Diana de Filippi, Lillian Elliott, Pat Hickman, Martie Holmer, Sarah Redfield, 1979-10-12-1979-11-04 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Lillian Elliot is Aaron Elliot's mother.
  - Board Games, 1993-2014
    - Blatz Game (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Includes board game and related materials
    - Blatz Game Board (oversized) (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Oversized board.
    - Richmond Board Game, 1993-1994; McPheeters, Sam; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Includes board game materials and Aaron Cometbus note
    - Suckcesspool Board Game, 2001-2014 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      Contains paste-ups for the game and issue of Apology containing essay about the game by Aaron Cometbus.
- Sound Recordings, 1982-2009
  - 7" Vinyl Records, 1988-2008; SR-20751-20758 (Box 14)
    Contains: "Songs of Wrath and Optimism" by Astrid Oto, "Untitled" by Astrid Oto, "House Band Feud" by The Blank Fight, "Untitled" by Cleveland Bound Death Sentence, "Sleep, What's That? EP" by Crimpshrine, "On the Waterfront EP" by Crybaby MacArthur, "Untitled" by Pinhead Gunpowder, and "Redmond Shooting Stars" by Redmond Shooting Stars.
  - Cassettes, 1982-2009; TR-15977-15993 (Box 15)
    Contains an introduction by Aaron Cometbus and the cassette tapes: "Banned in R.C." by Blatz, "Rokken' Like Dokken'" by The Blottos, "Live at the Metropolis" by Brap Smears, "Brent's T.V." by Brent's T.V., "Through Our Eyes" by Complete Disorder, "Untitled" by Crimpshrine, "Driller Killers" by Driller Killers, "Arbgabdo Baby!" by Fleshies, "Eartraining for Corporates" by Harbinger, "Jüke @ Gilman" by Jüke, "Untitled" by Maniax, "Bloody Marys…" by Premarital Sex, "It's Not Just a Band…It's a Lifestyle" by Soup, and "Pug's Not Dead" by Zombie Dogs. Also contains the compilation tapes "Gimme Cooties," "Absolutely Zippo Presents...'Time Capsule'," "Every Dog Has its Blues: The Bands of Lucky Dog," and "We Got Glue."
- Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1981-1991
  Arranged chronologically by letter date or post-marked envelope date where available.
  - Introduction to the Letters to Cometbus Magazine pt. 1, 1981-1989, 2017-03; Cometbus, Aaron (Box 13, Folder a)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine Packets, 1981-1983 (Box 16)
    Early letters stapled together with corresponding envelopes.
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1984-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Cometbus Magazine, 1980-1989; Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Unmatched Envelopes, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Unmatched envelopes, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Unmatched Envelopes, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Unmatched Envelopes, 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Unmatched Envelopes, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)